One dream.
One wish.
If you want it, gotta go over the top.
Setting sail and heading for the unknown.
Cutting through the
winds and waves as I go.
Gotta keep it up, never stopping, no.
Cause I'm aiming to get there first, yeah.
It's all or nothing, no time to worry.
Do it later, right now I'm living free.
When your foes look like
they will overwhelm you.
It means your heart's saying
this is what you can't do.
Despite all that to run is not an option.
Once they're closed, I
feel the satisfaction.
You think I'm rude,
here's my appreciation.
When things are getting
tough, just gotta smile.
If you are going on your way.
And you're looking for
a fresh, brand new day.
Then make sure your only
thought you have is.
Yes, I can.
As you're on your way.
Moth maps will be made.
Yes, with every step that you will take.
Just look at all you've been through.
Look ahead at new horizons.
In view shining brightly.
Oh, who knows what's waiting for you?
Dream living, that's the way.
Make like a hurricane.
Now, got to make your mark today.
One dream, one wish.
Your dreams don't run away.
Go for the knockout.
Over the top.
All right, let's move out.
Papa, what's wrong?
You didn't, did you?
Now room
and scan.
I warned you, and you
did it anyway. Sorry.
They looked so good,
and I couldn't resist.
Am I going to die? What? No.
But you will have the runs.
That's why I told you not to
eat the fish from the river.
Damn it. Bad timing.
Please forgive me.
Don't play cute with me.
What a pain.
Bunch of troublemakers.
You better not blow this Straw Hat.
Lay low.
They're rebels!
Hey boss, we got a group of
rebels here in the town square.
Looks like that guy who killed
the magistrate is with them.
Worry not, I'm on my way now.
One of them has a straw
hat around his neck.
Yes, that's right.
No matter what, do not engage.
They are far too strong for you to defeat.
How could you do that to our champion?
You shouldn't even be here.
Let's carve him up.
I'm guessing tama is the little brat.
General hold 'em took captive.
You want her back?
Good luck.
It was a sumo fight and
now it's a sword fight. Ha!
Where's Tom?
Give her back now!
And he threw the damn scabbard again.
Sham!
Whatever shall I do?
Enough with the act.
You can take care of yourself.
You're saying I should cut them down?
Cut them.
If you want to save the
kid, don't hold back.
Horotama...
We'll rescue you.
Give Tom a back!
I'd bring it quick if I were you.
Before you're dead.
Now, who's next?
It seems to be quite the commotion.
I'm hungry!
Stop it. That's shameful.
Show your pride as a man of Wano.
Even if it hurts, you mustn't carry on so.
I'm so hungry!
Don't you start crying too!
Alter to help!
Help!
It's my child! We need an herb!
Quickly!
They were hungry, and
they drink from the river!
Anything just to fill their belly!
That's terrible!
Come inside with me!
All right, time to collect.
Put your harvest on the pallet.
Oh, please, sir.
Right. Your money.
Five silver?
When you're done, slink back to
Okobori town and take the back way!
Wait, I beg of you, I can't possibly feed
my family on early fights over a week?
We can't even buy fresh
water with this—who cares?
And stop!
stop Touch me!
What's your boss's name?
It's Oldema.
Oldema.
Oldema. Oldema.
Boldema, huh?
Oh, no, there's a fire!
That way!
Call the firefighters!
You better keep your hands off
Tama, or I'm gonna make you pay!
I'm sick of waiting!
Give Tama back!
Come on, Boldama!
I'm right here, so stop your damn yelling!
It's about time, so you're the boss!
Hand over Tama, Buldemur!
The name's Hold 'em!
Who's Buldemur?
Kick his ass!
You done hiding?
I couldn't hide if I wanted to!
You destroyed my house with a
damn sumo wrestler, no less.
I don't know if you were trying to use
urashima as a human missile
to destroy my house,
but you did a fine job of it!
Who the hell are you people?
Good
We'll save you!
Actually, I think I know what's going on.
You work under that thief,
Shutenmaru, don't you?
But you should have known better
than to screw with Bekori Town!
Shutenmaru?
Never heard of him!
It's your time right, playing dumb?
Either way seems you're
here for this girl.
Then you'd better not move one full step,
and I'll crush her bones in an instant!
What do I do?
Damn it!
No way.
His stomach's a lion?
General Hold 'em just showed up.
Looks like he's talking
to that Straw Hat guy.
I think I could break
out any minute, boss.
What now?
You got any orders for us?
Wait for me.
I'm at the town gate now.
Captain Hawkins is joining the party.
There was a big fire in town.
But what caused it?
I'm fading.
Don't leave me.
Must be Straw Hats.
Actually, yeah, you're right.
There he is.
I'll save you, Tama. Stay strong.
What, you think I'm just
gonna give her back?
How dumb are you?
This is bad.
Open the gate.
Gate opening.
Another lovely display.
The selection today is delectable.
Thank you, General Speed.
So would you like to examine the goods?
They're piled up right here behind you.
I'm looking now.
My range of vision is 350 degrees.
I don't even need to turn.
Now that's horsepower!
Why, thank you!
That smile has horsepower, too!
The fire bell? Fire! Fire!
Coming through!
We claim this fire in the name of Igory,
the best firefighting squad in town!
This is a wreck.
Stop showing up!
Wait a sec, this is Hold
'em's mansion, isn't it?
What caused all of this destruction?
Just look behind you, General!
I'm looking now!
Do I need to explain my
wide range of vision again?
Surely the sumo event
wasn't the cause of this.
Something's amiss.
Hahaha!
Yes!
Please hurry!
Hey, Tama!
You'll be fine!
Huh?
Oh, will she?
And how are you going to save her? Hm?
Hahaha!
Thought I told you.
If you move a single inch, it's all over.
Didn't you notice?
I've got a lion in my belly!
His name's Kami-jiro, and
he's ready to start chomping!
We'll save you!
Don't listen to him, Otama!
Alright, Boldama!
You let her go or I'll kick your ass!
You think I'm scared of you?
You can't even get my name right!
And it's hold them by the way,
you
just keep running your mouth, you idiot.
Nothing you say is
gonna make me back down.
Why do you want this stupid
brat so bad in the first place?
Maybe you're looking to use our
Devil Fruit ability just like me.
Is that it?
You're all gonna be my hostages soon.
Chutenmaru's next.
He'll come for you.
That!
this is worrisome give it up already he's
the head of your thief
brigade and you know it
those farm robberies have been a real pain
lately admit it they're
the work of the atamayama
thieves brigade aren't they maybe it was
just dumb luck but you
beat urashima somehow
that means you're probably
high ranking in the brigade
what are you talking about man
lufitado i don't know if it's wise to
anger him in this situation he's
pretty angry already though who cares
what i mean is that we don't
want this matter to escalate
He's strong, but that's not my concern
It's not Holden himself who strikes fear
into the hearts of the citizens here
It's the man above him
A terrifying member of the Beast
Pirates One of Kaido's top officers
The true ruler of Kuri Is Jack the Drought
wait we know him he's the guy who messed
up zo isn't he huh oh yeah that big creep
who poisoned king
cat and king dog but
that elephant kicked his ass in the end
This ship got wrecked and
we sank into the ocean.
He's got to be dead.
Cat? Dog?
Elephant?
They can't mean that literally.
We heard Jack had a wreck at sea.
But he's most certainly not dead.
In fact, he showed up here in
Bekori Town just a few days ago.
So, if we push too hard against
Hold 'em, then Jack retaliates.
The town will be left in ruins.
He is known as a living
disaster, after all.
No matter what, we can't let that happen.
How's that supposed to be fair?
Jerks, you can't just hold the
whole town hostage like that!
Hey!
What are you guys going
on about over there?
What's the matter?
I thought you were going to
take your little friend back.
Maybe kick my ass a bit? Oh, wait!
I'm the one holding all the cards here!
Cause I can do this!
Stop it!
Leave her alone!
What's wrong with you?
That's some sweet music, huh?
Give me some more!
The anguished cries of the lowly!
If you're mad, remember,
this is all your fault!
Should have thought twice
before you wrecked my house!
What's going on, Hold 'em?
You need some help or what?
The food treasure bar just rollin' in!
Let's grab our group, fellas!
I'm starving!
I could go for a fief like that.
Those are the supplies
from the Paradise Farm.
The water there is clean, so the
food's delicious and safe to eat.
Why is it only for them?
Zoro!
Can you handle that?
Yep. What?
I'll save Tama!
Huh? Huh?
Sorry, short notice, but we're
stealing the food and running.
What?
Just like that?
It's probably going to
piss him off pretty bad,
but it beats smashing his face in, right?
Hey, look!
Hawkins is here!
We need your help!
The enemy's too tough!
And what is Holden doing?
He's confronting the intruders
at the plaza in the 4th District!
He's not picking up, it seems.
I'm afraid I'm going to have to
ask you to stop, Basil Hawkins.
Who are you?
He's strong.
Wano is closed off from
the rest of the world.
With no information from the
outside, but Hawkins knows our faces.
I have to erase him.
This next part will be fun for
me, at least not so much for you!
Capture one, but you can kill the rest!
Make it bloody!
Show them no mercy!
Not so fast!
Remember, we have this brat as a hostage,
so I'd put that sword away if I were you.
What have you done?
You'll endanger her, otama!
Whoa, that's cold—decided
you don't need the girl.
Back after all?
Huh, fine by me.
Huh, I'm sure Kamijito's
grateful for the snack.
Go ahead, chew her up!
up
What the?
She disappeared!
That bastard!
I didn't even see him!
Tomijiro, you had one job, you dummy!
You good?
Let's go, okay?
Thank you.
Sorry I kept you waiting so long.
You're about to get a
flaming blade to the face!
No one's ever escaped my
trick mechanism, sword!
And you won't be the first!
Hellfire Ants Go!
Well, that was easy.
Don't scream.
You're coming with me.
Oh, yeah?
If you think I'm lying,
you're gonna be sorry!
I mean it!
Put those swords down now!
You're reasonable after all.
Are you sure about this now?
Stay right there.
Don't move while I beat you to death!
Big lady.
I'm not gonna help you!
Don't you care about her,
you heartless bastard!
Dumb girl!
If you'll excuse me.
What should I do now?
Take care of your side. Right.
Whoa!
Hey!
Hey, dog!
Get over here, quick!
My, what a gentleman.
Hey, what happened to your cheek?
Oh it's no big deal.
It just got yanked on
by some pliers is all.
That guy's dumb.
You can't make Cape
Dongle come out like that.
He what?
Give me a second Tama!
Tired of running away?
It's okay! I'm fine!
You don't need to fight!
Saving me was enough!
Good! Let's go!
Lionfire, it's time to roar!
And now, I'll finish you off!
I've got one more trick
to show, so don't blink!
Come back!
Red Hawk!
I don't know.